{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "When did the season start?",
      "answer": "October 10"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "When did the season end?",
      "answer": "18 april"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "What team suspended their operation in the 2023-24 season?",
      "answer": "Arizona Coyotes"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which team won the regular season?",
      "answer": "Farjestad BK"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "How many points are the winning team awarded in regulation time?",
      "answer": "Three points"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "When did the regular season start and end?",
      "answer": "September 2023, March 2024"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "When did Meta release Llama-3?",
      "answer": "April 18, 2024"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "How many model sizes were trained for the first version of LLaMA?",
      "answer": "Four"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which three model sizes did Meta train and release Llama-2 with?",
      "answer": "7, 13 and 70 billion parameters"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "What does it say in the header?",
      "answer": "T, LLM WIKI"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "What does it say in the footer?",
      "answer": "B, GPT"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Which model was praised in 2023 for its increased accuracy and for its multimodal capabilities?",
      "answer": "GPT-4"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Which is the most powerful open LLM as of January 2024 and is it as powerful as GPT-4?",
      "answer": "Mixtral 8x7b, not as powerful as GPT-4"
    }
  ]
}